Assalamu Alaikum. I told you if I have any updated news I will tell you it sounds
like 48 hours a building Mansour was in it was attacked by the Israel. I just
want one thing a message to Mr. Justin Trudeau to help me to go there to
Rafah to be able to see my son and to look for him and if he can send the Red
cross to that area and find find him that will be very good help from him I need
his help to go to Rafah I have a PR Canadian PR and a Jordanian passport and I
need to go there as soon as possible to Rafah to see my son please help me to do
that and please all of you pray for my son's safety and return I'm sure he's
okay and your prayers will bring him back but please help me to go there and see
him that's this message to Justin Trudeau thank you very much